{
    "subject": "resource/Murder_of_Elisa_Izquierdo",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Manhattan",
    "human_readable": "Elisa Izquierdo was murdered in Manhattan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9492718577384949,
            "question": "Where was Elisa Izquierdo murdered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.813235878944397,
            "question": "In what location did Elisa Izquierdo's murder occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743561863899231,
            "question": "Is there any information available about who was responsible for Elisa Izquierdo's murder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7455152869224548,
            "question": "What happened to Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713427305221558,
            "question": "Did the murder of Elisa Izquierdo receive media attention?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557032465934753,
            "question": "Was Elisa Izquierdo a victim of violence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.627247154712677,
            "question": "Was Elisa Izquierdo's murder investigated by law enforcement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6045337915420532,
            "question": "What is known about the circumstances surrounding Elisa Izquierdo's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28203171491622925,
            "question": "Are there any organizations that advocate for victims of violence like Elisa Izquierdo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2055680751800537,
            "question": "Are there any public records or reports related to Elisa Izquierdo's case?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elisa Izquierdo was murdered in Manhattan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3742_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any organizations that advocate for victims of violence like Elisa Izquierdo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3742_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about the circumstances surrounding Elisa Izquierdo's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3742_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Elisa Izquierdo's murder investigated by law enforcement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3742_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3742_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is stated in multiple files that Elisa Izquierdo was a six-year-old girl who was murdered by her mother on the Lower East Side, and later died at the age of 6 after being beaten to death in her Manhattan apartment."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the murder of Elisa Izquierdo, stating that she died on November 22, 1995, in Manhattan after being beaten by her mother. This supports the statement that Elisa Izquierdo was murdered in Manhattan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}